[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[In my prime]
[Episode 16]
Auntie,
could you lend me some money
to pay for my tuition?
When I get a job and make money
in the future,
I will
absolutely pay you back with interest.
Hello?
Hello. Auntie, it...
it is me, Qi Shi.
Oh, it's you, Qi Shi.
How did you do
on the college entrance exam?
I... performed poorly.
That's no big deal.
I only finished middle school,
yet I managed to become a big boss.
Many staffers of my company
are college grads.
They know much about theories, but lack
practical skills.
In my opinion, you are
better off entering
the real world early.
Diplomas are nothing
but just pieces of paper.
However high your degree is,
you'll still have to apply
what you've learned, right?
You can succeed anywhere
as long as you have the right skills.
You gave me a call.
Has something come up?
I don't want to go to a special school!
I'll stay in the yard all night
if Mom still doesn't allow me
to go to school!
Does drinking soy sauce
really make you darker?
She really knows
how to solve this equation.
This is incredibly rare!
Since I was little,
they called me "White-Haired Girl"
and called me a monster.
I refused to just take it,
so I fought them.
I ran for class monitor
and asked to join the sports meet
just in order to prove myself
to be the same as everyone of you.
I just wanted a chance,
a fair chance to compete.
I might lose.
But even so, I wanted
a chance to lose fair and square.
Today, let me
tell you some more words.
The wise are free from doubt.
The benevolent are free from worry.
The brave are free from fear.
Diplomas are nothing
but just pieces of paper.
However high your degree is,
you'll still have to apply
what you've learned, right?
You can succeed anywhere
as long as you have the right skills.
Qi Shi,
where are you off to?
I'm not repeating the year.
These are useless now.
So I'll go sell them.
Give them to me.
Aren't you too young
to give up on your education?
Come here.
Take this money.
-Retake the college entrance exam.
-No.
-No, I can't.
-Take it.
If you need anything,
just let me know.
I will support you unconditionally.
Just take it.
Thank you, Mr. Cao.
But I really don't need the money.
Qi Shi,
whatever between me and your parents
has nothing to do with you kids.
Just consider
the money as a loan from me.
You can pay me back
when you are able to someday, alright?
Mr. Cao,
you're truly nice.
I'm not refusing your money
because of the grudges
between you and my parents.
I've just thought it through.
There are many paths
to choose from in life.
Going to college isn't the only option.
You see, many successful people
dropped out of school.
Didn't they go on top
of the world in the end?
Besides,
there are night schools
and adult self-study exams.
As long as I want to learn,
I can do it anywhere.
But instead of going
to college, what can you do?
I'll step out into the real world.
I'm leaving home
to make my own way.
Where can you possibly go
when you leave home?
You're just a young girl.
I haven't decided yet.
I just want to prove to my mom
that she was wrong.
My life won't
turn out like what she said.
I have the right
to choose my own path.
And I firmly believe
that I can make it to the end.
If you ever need money,
just let me know.
Congratulations, Qi Zhi.
You've brought honor to your country.
Thank you, President. Thank you!
[Shuttles
between Qingwu Town and Jiangyuan City]
Sweetie.
Have you really thought it through?
Take this money.
Remember to treat
yourself well out there.
I'm not capable of much.
This is all I can do to help you.
Where did this money come from?
You kept a secret stash
behind my mom's back again,huh?
What secret stash?
I saved this up bit by bit
by secretly collecting and selling scrap.
I meant it as my pocket money.
Oh, right.
And this.
It's secondhand.
I've tested all the functions.
It works fine.
If you can, call home often.
I put some credit on it, so don't worry
about the phone bill.
I'll take them both.
It's time I got on the bus, Dad.
Hold on, hold on.
You look great.
Take care
of your health out there.
I'm leaving.
Go ahead.
Sweetie,
if things don't go well
in the provincial capital,
just come back.
We'll always have a place
for you at home.
Don't worry, Dad.
That day will never come.
Just wait till I make it big.
Then I'll create a life of luxury for you.
Go home.
Go home now!
Our family used to be so happy.
Even though
life was a bit hard,
at least both our kids were at home,
so we had
something to strive for.
Now our son is away,
and our daughter has also left.
What's the point of our lives?
Though our kids are away,
I'm still here with you, aren't I?
How does that saying go?
When things hit rock bottom...
Good days come
once the bad days are over.
You should always look on the bright side.
Things will get better.
They will.
♪ The wind blew through our hair ♪
♪ The story slowly grew complicated ♪
♪ We didn't become anyone's legend ♪
♪ We only learned to grow up in the rain ♪
♪ Are we to blame fate? ♪
♪ Adulthood is bandaging your own fall ♪
♪ Rented rooms, the last bus home ♪
Take this once a day.
♪ What does the future hold? ♪
♪ It's been long since I last had
the guts to say I feared ♪
♪ Though we have nothing,
we still bustle about ♪
♪ Because the answer is clear
as long as you are around ♪
♪ The old dreams are now covered in dust ♪
♪ But it's okay ♪
♪ Some things are better off
staying the way they are ♪
[Welcome to Haizhou]
Look, I do the same work
in Haizhou as I did in Qingwu,
but I can make
500 yuan more every month here.
Haizhou is a great place.
I'm just not sure what job
♪ Who hasn't panicked
in this fast-paced world? ♪
my education can get me.
In big cities,
skills matter more than degrees.
♪ All I see is the look in your eyes ♪
My niece only finished middle school,
but she runs a company now.
She even bought a villa for her family.
Really?
Of course.
♪ If there's nothing left tomorrow ♪
Haizhou really is an amazing place.
♪ I'll still walk home with you ♪
I can't hold up.
Sorry.
We really
don't have any hiring plans.
I've been to every office
in this building.
I... must find a job now,
or I'll end up sleeping on the streets.
Well...
How about this?
I'm begging you.
Please just let me see
the company's...
Seek opportunities
elsewhere.
Did you just say
you couldn't do a tiny task like this?
What?
You want me to turn on the computer
and make the slides for you?
Zhou!
Come over!
Mail this.
Got it, Mr. He.
Take my post as the manager then!
Get lost if you can't do your job!
I'm competent!
Very much so.
Who are you?
Hello, Mr. He.
My name is Qi Shi.
I hope
you can give me a chance
to solve your problems
and assist you...
in many, many things!
This is a legitimate company
we're running,
not some street stall.
We won't hire you simply
because you stick around
and say a few nice words.
I know.
This is a big company after all.
I heard you're short-staffed right now.
How about this?
I'll work here
without pay.
Could you consider giving
me a chance
to interview if you find me
qualified?
If I assign a helper
to you for those slides,
can you finish them in one day?
Yes.
So you can finish your work
with a helper now?
Okay.
Stay with her
and work hard.
Come see me when you're done.
Thank you, Mr. He!
Let's go.
Your company
is quite large.
Do you know how to make slides?
What?
It's a computer software, right?
I can learn.
I could make them myself
in the time it takes to teach you.
Then what else can I help you with?
You can leave now.
This is my job anyway.
I'll just hang in there
and get it done.
No way.
I already said I'd help you.
I must
keep my word.
I don't know how to make slides,
but I can help you organize
documents and stuff.
I can do all that.
Or I can buy food for you and get you
water.
I...
I'll do anything
you tell me to,
except for using the toilet for you.
Actually, you are...
quite interesting.
How about this?
Extract all the underlined
key information
from...
from this material,
type it into the computer,
and organize it into
a structured document.
Then I'll teach you
how to make slides
based on that document
and form a report
for the leaders to review.
Consider it done.
Cao Xin, hurry up!
Class is beginning.
It's a required course.
That old man Wang will call the roll.
Fine. See you in the back row.
[Finance]
He still won't see us?
Okay, I got it.
He must be blaming me.
Blaming me for stopping him
from dating Cao Si,
for being useless and unable
to get him a lighter sentence,
and for neglecting his sister,
leaving her to struggle alone
in Haizhou.
It's all my fault!
My fault!
Huo Qinglian,
what are you doing?
You are famous around here
for being tough.
Are you hitting
and scolding yourself
now that you can't
v-vent it out on others?
What's wrong with that?
Can't I do that?
You can.
You surely can.
As long as you want to.
You're Huo Qinglian.
What have you ever feared?
Nothing.
Everything will be fine.
Has Qi Shi contacted you?
She's a good girl,
keeping me updated all the time.
She texted me just a couple of days ago,
saying
that she already got a job
and settled down.
She works in a big company now.
What big company? Did you ask?
No, I didn't.
You should have.
She's a young girl
with no degree or experience.
What big company would hire her?
I hope she didn't run into scammers.
You can't just believe
everything she says.
You know?
What's that smile for?
I'm talking to you.
Give her a call right now.
Ask her where she is,
where she lives,
and where she works.
Or else, go visit her yourself.
Why don't you call her?
Why should I?
I'm busy right now.
You've been staying
in bed all the time lately.
And now you're saying you're busy?
Who's going to pay off
our debts if I don't
work hard?
Neither of our kids is settled yet.
Make room for me.
The family will truly fall apart
if I don't begin making money now.
Honey,
now that's the correct attitude.
Right?
This is the Huo Qinglian I know.
Let's
make our family business
bigger and stronger,
while we wait for our kids to come home.
Call
Qi Shi later.
And send some money
to Qi Zhi.
I'd hate for him to suffer in there.
Yes, madam.
[Times Square World Trade Center]
Mr. He,
this is my application
for regular employment.
I've attached the planning data
for the marketing department's
three hit products
from last quarter.
Also,
can I get my salary
for the internship period now?
What do you mean by this?
Don't you know
what I mean?
Here's the thing, Qi Shi.
I let you work in our company
simply out of pity.
But you only finished high school,
and you can't even make
a basic slide.
Do you think
you can stay in the company
just by some
effortless sweet-talking?
My money
doesn't grow on trees.
Right?
You did give me a chance.
The fact is...
I passed the job interview
-before...
-Hold on.
I prepared the people
who interviewed you.
Otherwise, you think they'd hire you,
someone who can't even
differentiate
between sales per square meter
and average transaction value,
or franchising
and distributorship?
Everything else aside,
in these past few months,
how many silly mistakes
were caused by your ignorance?
Do I need to remind you of them
one by one?
Mr. He,
look, I...
In addition,
you have a severe case of albinism.
You think people won't notice that
when you have
makeup and a wig on?
How can you represent
the company's image looking like this?
How do you meet clients
and negotiate with them?
Who will take responsibility
if the clients who don't know better
are scared away?
Alright.
I have tons
of things to do.
I'm swamped.
Don't come back to work tomorrow.
That's it.
[The 5th Beining University
Debate Competition]
Now, let's enter
the free debate session.
We've made
our argument clear.
Adversity
builds character better,
as it gives people the courage
to overcome
difficulties and setbacks.
Let's take those around us
as examples.
The students of humble origins who bravely
overcame adversity
and entered our university
are the best proof.
Dear opposing debater,
there is a fact
that cannot be ignored. That is,
poor students admitted to our school
account for only 15%
of the total.
I do not deny
that for a few, adversity does
help build up character better.
But compared to the positive mindset
brought by favorable circumstances,
adversity
often wears down one's will
and leaves them devastated.
Look at these figures,
15% versus 85%.
The data you provided
exactly proves
that poverty makes it hard
to reach the top,
while success comes easier
in favorable conditions.
Mr. He,
I know I've made mistakes,
but I've been working diligently
for the past six months
without slacking off.
You said you had to delay the payroll
due to cash flow issues.
But I should at least get my pay
for working here
for six months.
Do you have to nag on and on?
You're just a high school graduate.
You don't meet the company's
hiring requirements at all.
Also, by
withholding the fact
that you have a major illness
from the company, I can sue you anytime.
How dare you ask me for you pay?
Pack up your things
and leave the staff dorm immediately.
Otherwise,
I won't show you any mercy.
Get out!
I agree with
the opposing debater.
Figures are cold.
I'd like to take a girl
I know as an example.
I grew up with a neighbor.
In terms of grades alone,
she was almost always in first place.
She definitely met
all the standards for success.
But she didn't finish
the college entrance exam
due to a family emergency.
She couldn't even repeat the year.
So she had no choice
but to enter society early.
Compared to us,
who are talking eloquently
on a college debate stage now,
she is probably
struggling to make a living.
Given that, think about this.
Who should be considered a success,
me in favorable circumstances,
or her in adversity?
Thank you.
Qi Shi.
Qi Shi!
Wait, Qi Shi!
You left something behind.
Thank you.
Come here.
Let me tell you the truth.
Since the first day
you started working here,
Mr. He has never thought
about keeping you.
It's typical of him to use this trick.
He just exploited you as an intern
for free labor.
Not just you,
but several college students
were dismissed
with various excuses
previously.
It's illegal to fire us
without proper cause.
Even if Mr. He hires new staffers,
he still has to pay compensation
for wrongful termination.
Don't get all worked up.
Given your condition,
it's a bit hard to find a job.
But there will always be a way out.
I didn't mean to
keep my albinism a secret.
I can just work as well
with this condition.
It's just...
that I didn't go to college,
and that it's so hard
for me to get a job.
Listen.
Though we were colleagues
for just six months,
I do think of you as a smart girl
and a fast learner.
You are no less
than those college students.
Besides,
from my professional
perspective as a designer,
I'd say you have a great aesthetic.
If you want to stay in the industry
of women's fashion...
I got to know an older lady some time ago.
She's planning
to close her shop lately.
So, she needs to dump some stock,
even at a discount.
How about...
you take it over
and resell it?
That could be a way out.
I'll do it.
I'm up for it.
This is great. Thank...
I-I'm sorry.
My illness...
doesn't bother you?
I do have basic common sense.
Alright?
Okay.
Yuanyuan,
you're the first friend
I made in Haizhou.
May our paths cross again.
That will happen.
Off you go.
Goodbye.
[Dear ringtone user,
since today is your birthday,
we're offering you one month
of free ringtone replacement]
[Change it to Can't Help Loving You]
Honey,
look, our shop has stepped
on the right track now.
I'm just thinking...
maybe we should move to Haizhou.
We can replicate
our successful business mode
at that place.
You see,
it's much bigger there
with a higher population.
So it must be
easier to do business there than here.
Besides,
haven't you always
wanted to move there?
You think I have no idea?
You want to move there
s-so you can check on our daughter, right?
Am I the only one missing her?
Don't you miss her too?
Otherwise, why would you fry so many
mushrooms?
I fried them for you!
I fried them just for you.
Make sure you finish
all of them yourself.
Okay.
I'll eat them.
W-What about the buns?
Are they also just for me?
Then I'd say I'm very lucky.
Stop saying that.
How are you lucky?
It's been over six months,
yet our daughter has never answered
your calls,
and our son wouldn't  meet with you.
After living for such a long time,
you are stuck with me
at the end of the day.
What's the point of our lives?
To be honest,
I have a hunch
that Qi Shi will give me
a call today.
Come on, stop with it.
The buns are ready.
Pack them up quickly.
Lingzhi's cousin is delivering
goods to Haizhou later.
Ask him to take the food there.
What about the fried mushrooms?
It's a pity
that we're too far away from Beining.
Otherwise,
I'll definitely have these
brought to Cao Xin.
Today is his birthday.
He must be craving these.
Our children have all grown up.
We can't reach or see them anymore.
Even if we want to show them we care,
we don't know where to start.
Dad.
Son,
did you get the birthday gift
I sent you?
Yes, I did.
I got it yesterday.
Have you opened it yet?
I had classes all day today.
I haven't had time to open it yet.
No worries.
I just placed
some study materials in it.
I've checked online.
The finance program
at MacDonald University
is really, really good.
You need to start
planning right now.
Make sure you master both
the language and your major.
You will go abroad
for further studies
the moment you graduate.
Got it, Dad.
Cao Xin!
-You are really something.
-Look.
Impressive, man.
Your birthday is known
to all the girls
in the School of Economics.
Wait, how did you
get all this stuff?
Didn't I tell the dorm supervisor
to reject these?
The dorm supervisor did as you said.
But we dared not refuse the girls.
Think about it.
The debate competition
has shown that the girls
in the School of Economics
are sharp-tongued.
For the sake of unity
and the friendship among fellow students,
we had no choice
but to accept
the girls' gifts
on your behalf.
Your...
Is this how you treat a good friend?
Look how many items you took.
Hey, bro...
Look at this trophy of yours.
You're good at everything
and you always rank first.
You're the pride
of Room 206.
Exactly!
Fine then.
I'll treat you guys to dinner,
okay?
Just stop teasing me,
will you?
-Sure.
-No problem.
That was what we waited to hear.
I'm on the phone with my dad.
Keep it down, guys.
Dad.
Son, you are
having dinner with your classmates
tonight, right?
Do you have enough money?
Yes, yes.
I just received a scholarship.
Great.
Have a good time celebrating with them.
Is it Xin?
Yes.
Well...
Son,
you really should spend more time
with your classmates when you're free.
See if there is a girl
who is right for you.
You're a college student now.
I won't object to you dating someone
as long as it doesn't affect
your studies.
That's right, Xin!
Listen to me.
You must study hard.
You can find
all the answers in books!
Got it, Grandpa.
Take care of yourself.
Alright.
I'm hanging up.
Bye.
He hung up.
Of course he did.
Dad,
stop talking about superstitions
with young people.
They just don't
believe that stuff.
Dongfang,
I keep thinking about one thing lately.
In the past, every year,
Xin's birthday always came
right after Si's.
Time to feed the chickens.
Happy birthday.
Why do I have to celebrate my birthday
with Cao Xin every year?
Why can't we just buy a cake
and celebrate
at home like we do it for Zhi?
You're so fussy.
You two share the same birthday.
It's more fun to celebrate together.
Sweetie,
come take a look.
What's this?
You're here.
Come on, take a look.
Here it goes.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Feifei!
Thank you.
Qingcheng.
I invited Qingcheng over.
Hope you don't mind an extra guest.
Isn't she Gu Qingcheng, the golden girl
of the School of Economics?
Your presence
has lightened up
this little cafeteria.
That's an exaggeration.
How could I steal
the spotlight from the birthday boy?
Not at all.
Have a seat.
Grab her a chair now.
Just take my seat.
Time to blow out the candles.
You two birthday stars,
make a wish.
What did you wish for?
Happy birthday!
-Happy birthday.
-Let's cut the cake!
Alright.
Come on.
There we go.
You're about to lose your front tooth.
Keep the flowers.
One for each kid.
Give it to Qi Shi first.
Okay, Qi Shi first.
Okay.
Here you are.
-This piece is for Cao Xin.
-Cao Xin!
Okay.
And this piece...
-is for Qi Zhi.
-Give it to Grandpa.
Okay. For Grandpa.
Give it to Grandpa.
-Alright, thanks.
-This is for the elderly.
T-Take it.
Cao Xin!
Take this out.
Come back here!
What just happened?
What wish did you make?
Nothing in particular.
I just thought of
a childhood friend.
I'd really like to spend
a birthday with her again.
A childhood friend?
You mean...
the neighbor
you mentioned at the debate?
Yes.
What does she do now?
We've been out of touch for a long time.
So I don't know.
If it's meant to be,
you'll see her again.
Perhaps.
Noodles for you.
Thank you,
ma'am.
A bowl of beef noodles!
Coming right up.
[Dad]
Sweetie,
today is your birthday.
Your mom made you fried mushrooms
and steamed buns.
We had them brought
to Haizhou for you.
You're still at the address you sent me
earlier, right?
Dad,
I'm no longer at that address.
As for the new address...
Hello?
Hello, Dad.
Sweetie,
you finally called.
I knew
my hunch was right.
Have you eaten birthday cake yet?
And those fried mushrooms
and steamed buns...
Have you got them?